https://www.wintranslation.com/privacy-policy/

skip to Main Content
MenuPrivacy Policywintranslation respects and protects the privacy of all persons that use our website. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission.Additionally, this Website may contain links to other sites that are outside of wintranslation control. These sites may have their own policies regarding privacy and you are encouraged to get acquainted with their Privacy Policy acts as well.Private information sharing and disclosurewintranslation will not sell or distribute your personal information to anyone.We may share limited personal information collected on the Website with our partners and third parties but only with your consent or if the specific content being read, downloaded, copied is provided by our partner company.We may disclose personal information when required by law or if in good faith we believe that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on the Website.Personal informationYou can access wintranslation website and browse it without providing your personal information. However, in order to benefit from some of the services offered on the Website, a user must provide personal information (including, but not limited to, your name, phone number or email address).Personal information collected on this Website is used primarily for the purpose it is requested, for presenting additional information about a chosen topic, or to provide you with additional information about similar services. In particular, contact information such as name and e-mail addresses can be used to provide users with more information about services that they have presented interest in.Limitation of liabilityYOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. NEITHER WINTRANSLATION, NOR ANY OF ITS AFFILIATES, OR ANY OTHER PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DELIVERING THE SITE WILL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR OTHER DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE MATERIALS ON THE SITE, INCLUDING DAMAGES CAUSED BY VIRUSES OR ANY INCORRECTNESS OR INCOMPLETENESS OF THE INFORMATION ON THE SITE, EVEN IF WINTRANSLATION HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH DAMAGES.Business Info2197 Riverside Dr
Suite #602
Ottawa, ON
K1H 7X3+1(877) 742-5982 (toll-free for U.S. and Canada)+1(613) 686-1278web@wintranslation.comSocial LinkstwitterfacebooklinkedinyoutuberssemailLinksHomeAbout UsBlogPressGet A QuoteContact Us
Translation Service Company Copyright © 1998-2020 wintranslationSitemapPrivacy PolicyWork With UsLanguages and Dialects
Back To Top×
